KHIN Channy

#18, 2002 Home St, Phnom Penh, KH, 12000

+855 77 38 9000

⊘ khinchannyofficial

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/channy-khin-a94a2679/

khinchanny@hotmail.com

09 Dec 2022

CHOKCHEY Finance

Head of IT

Phnom Penh, Cambodia

Dear Sir/Madam,

I am writing to apply for the **Head of IT** at **CHOKCHEY Finance** Systems+, as advertised on Website. I am confident that my 08 years of solid experience and diverse capabilities in projectmanagement make me an ideal candidate to successfully fulfill this position.

During my time worked as a **Business Systems Coordinator** at **Aprati Foods (Cambodia),** I was the second-in-charge to the Project Manager in leading a medium-sized development team. I was charged with the responsibility of helping oversee a range of critical projects from conception to delivery.

I was commended by my manager for demonstrating strong skills in:

- Proactively managing important and time-sensitive projects
- Developing innovative solutions to critical problems
- Balancing stakeholder expectations with those of the company
- Working collaboratively with other team members to establish efficient systems of operation

In my time at Aprati Foods (Cambodia), I was noted for having achieved the following:

- Executing a number of highly profitable projects
- Working with my team to manage the accounts of prestigious international brands and clients
- Possessing a strong understanding of statistics, quality improvement techniques
- Contributing successfully to Q & A testing, product, integration, and user documentations.

Furthermore, I have a strong academic background to ground my work. After completing my Bachelor of Computer Science at the AEU University, I plan to draw on these methodologies at Systems+ to effectively complete project scheduling, issue tracking, and resource management tasks.

I believe that the above qualities and experiences would make me a valuable addition to your company. If there is any more information you would like me to provide, please do not hesitate to contact me.

Sincerely,

KHIN CHANNY (Mr.)

Ps: Please find the CV enclosed



KHIN Channy

Status: Single

Nationality: Cambodian

DOB: 05-Oct-1989 DOP: Pursat Province Tell: +855 77 38 9000 Akhinchannyofficial

inhttps://www.linkedin.com/in/ channy-khin-a94a2679/

STRENGTHS

- Business Plan (FP)
- ERP Web Application

TRAINING

• Technology:

- ❖ Python 90%
- **❖** PHP___**80%**
- ❖ JavaScript___90%
- ❖ SQL Server 80%
- **❖** MySQL___**90%**
- ❖ Postgres SQL 80%
- **❖** Oracle **70%**
- ❖ Others Tech 50%

CONSULTANT ERP WEB

- ERPNext Web App
- Odoo Web Application
- ❖ Dynamics 365 BC
- Oracle Supply Chain & Manufacturing

EXPERIENCES

2021-2022 Business System Coordinator at Aprati Foods

- Coordinate all MRP/ERP projects and prioritize all incoming
- Explore new capabilities (new way to improve business via new technology)
- Collaborates with stakeholders to define, analyze and document information needs and business requirement
- Perform digital transformation analysis and modelling activities by interviewing process owners, users and other stakeholders to identify business process, existing system integration, optimize workflow, documents finding and recommend improvement
- Recommend and develop ERP solutions and system to address business issues and to meet the business requirements and strategies
- Coordinate discussion with cross-functional teams to define business and technical requirements, create and maintain thorough, up-to-date, functional and technical ERP systems documentation
- Implement and maintain ERP systems, provide user training, support, documents updates and administration
- Collaborate with other teams to ensure integration of design and functionality
- Visualize design, build and deploy BI solutions-able to turn those requirements into impactful dashboard in a way to drive better, more informed decisions for the company
- Monitor and measure effectiveness of MRP/ERP usage and recommend for improvement

2018-2021: ERPCam Solution

ERP Project Manager (2020-2021)

- Establishing ERP need via business process analysis and consultant
- Analysis existing infrastructure and performing IT System enhancement
- Customized programs & scripts, as well as configuring ERP
- Developing user-friendly functionalities and interfaces
- Installing ERP Software and ensuring seamless integration
- Performing diagnostic test and resolving issues to optimize
- Providing technical support and training ERP End-Users
- Preparing development progress updates & documenting ERP
- Adhering to company policies and industry regulations
- Keeping abreast of the latest ERP upgrades and offerings

REFFERENCE

- ❖ Mr. HUN Pheakday
- Family Economic Organization General
- hunpheakdey@yahoo.com
- **3** 017 26 65 98/ 098 82 66 698

Mr. BOU Phannarith

Deputy Director, CADP

* Tell: 0319388222

Mrs. Serak SAO

Program Assistant, Peace Corps Cambodia

* Tell: 012927230

RESULT PROJECT

- ❖ Supply Chain Management
- Inventory Management
- **❖** Sale Management
- Finance Management
- **❖** Manufacturing Application
- Project Management
- CRM Management
- ❖ HR & Payroll Management
- ❖ Others Website & Mobile App



IT Project Manager (2019-2020)

- Develop a detail project management plan to track project progress
- Define the overall scope of the project and priorities the task of the project
- Manage project expectation with external and internal stakeholder
- Mentor and supervise project team member
- Coordinate and monitor projects through the entire project lifecycle
- Manage project performance with appropriate KPIs
- Excellent written and verbal communication skills, with the ability to lead and motivate
- A high level of organizational skills and attention to detail
- The ability to work under pressure and meet deadlines
- Ensure project tasks are executed and reviewed within scope

Scrum Master Manager (2018-2019)

- Manage each project's scope and timeline
- Coordinate sprints, retrospective meetings and daily stand-ups
- Coach team members in Agile frameworks
- Facilitate internal communication and effective collaboration
- Be the point of contact for external communications (e.g., from customers or stakeholders)
- Work with product owners to handle backlogs and new requests
- Resolve conflicts and remove obstacles that occur
- Help teams implement changes effectively
- Ensure deliverables are up to quality standards at the end of each sprint
- Guide development teams to higher scrum maturity
- Help build a productive environment where team members 'own' the product and enjoy working on it
- Create a health and motiving work environment and atmosphere
- Have been working is Jira, Microsoft Project 365 & Microsoft teams
- **2016-2018:** Project Manager at Life Education
- ❖ 2014-2016 Web Application of Plan B Cambodia
- **❖ 2010-2014 Studied at AEU (Computer Science)**
- *2008-2012 proven work at SCADP (NGO)

* HOBBIT

<u>Hobbit:</u> I am a perfectionist, and I am proud of it. I always polish peepers until they are shining like diamonds. I have learned to put my inner perfectionist to good use by creating assignments for those who need academic assistance.